I...
（奈々生(ななみ)）
私 必要とされてない
am not...
needed.
ah ah ah ah
Nanami...
（巴衛(ともえ)）
奈々生
奈々生…
Nanami!
Where have you gone?
（巴衛）
どこへ行った… 奈々生！
ah ah ah ah
Nanami!
Hang in there, Master Mizuki!
（虎徹(こてつ)）
瑞希(みずき)殿 しっかり！
What is that supposed to mean?
All I'm doing is throwing sake around.
（瑞希）
しっかりったって
神酒まくだけだよ
Take that! And that!
えい！　えい！
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
（奈々生）
私… 行くとこない
I...
have nowhere to go.
Oh, hey, Tomoe.
（瑞希）
あっ！　ちょっと 巴衛君
僕一人に重労働させておいて
屋根の上で何やって… えっ？
You're making me do all the work,
and you're just hanging out on the roof?
きつね火 奈々生を捜せ！
Foxfires, find Nanami!
（瑞希）
奈々生ちゃん いなくなったの？
Nanami's... gone?
What?! I'm coming too!
えーっ！　僕も行くよ！
（虎徹）
あーっ！　瑞希殿
社の しょう気が！
Oh, Master Mizuki! What about the miasma?
（瑞希）
はい これ
Here you go!
What?
（鬼切(おにきり)･虎徹）
えっ？
Use that!
（瑞希）
それで頑張って
What?! You cannot be serious!
（鬼切）えっ そんな！
（虎徹）わ… 我々が？
U-Us?!
Whoa! It is coming, Onikiri!
（虎徹）
わっ！　来た 鬼切！
（鬼切）
わわっ！
あっち行け あっち行け！
Go away! Go away!
Oh, dear.
（乙比古(おとひこ)）
あらら
神使２人も職場放棄？
どうするの このしょう気
The familiars abandoned their posts too?
What about the miasma?
まあ
すぐ回収してもいいんだけど…
Well, I could easily retrieve it, but...
I think I'd rather wait and see
how things go for a little longer.
この際 もう少し
様子を見ててあげようかしら
（乙比古）
ああ
なんて心優しい風神かしらね 私！
Aren't I the sweetest kindhearted wind god ever?
（磯辺(いそべ)）ＹＯ ＹＯ ＹＯ♪
（御手洗）あっ それ！
Ya know?! Ya know?!
Us, ya know?!
Nanami!
奈々生ちゃ～ん
奈々生ちゃん いる？
Nanami, you there?
奈々生ちゃん？
Nanami?
（きつね火１）
巴衛様
Master Tomoe.
We have searched everywhere, but we cannot find Lady Nanami anywhere.
（きつね火２）
八方捜しましたが―
奈々生様の行方は
ようとして知れず
（きつね火３）
気配も感じません
We cannot even sense her.
（きつね火４）
ひるな川筋にも姿はなく…
There were no signs of her along Hiruna River.
（きつね火５）
あの…
駅のほうにもいませんでした
Um, she wasn't over by the station either.
引き続き 捜してまいります！
We will continue to search for her!
（ミカゲ）
巴衛 街に行ってくるよ
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
（女子生徒１）
キャーッ！　巴衛君のご登校よ！
Tomoe's at school!
（女子生徒２）
今日は和服でらっしゃるわ！
He's in traditional clothes today!
What's the matter, fox?
（鞍馬(くらま)）
よう きつね
血相変えて遅刻か？
Stressed out because you're so late?
And what the heck?
それに何だ
Did you forget to change from your pajamas today?
今日は寝ぼけて
寝巻きのまま来たの…
おい てめえ きつね！
What the hell was that, fox?! How dare you ignore me?!
さっきは
よくも 俺様をスルーしやが…
You know, it's a crime to go into the ladies' room...
お前な 女トイレ入ったら犯罪者…
（巴衛）
奈々生
Nanami!
Hey!
（鞍馬）
おい！
どうした
What's going on?
てめえにしては
やけに余裕のねえ顔してるぜ
I know hostile is your thing,
but this is a bit much, even for you.
あっ 奈々生に何かあったのか
Did something happen to Nanami?
Wha—
お前には関係ない
It is none of your business.
Oh, crow, have you seen Nanami?
あっ 天狗(てんぐ)君
奈々生ちゃん見なかった？
いなくなっちゃったんだよね
We can't find her anywhere.
ぶふぁっ！
Tomoe, I didn't see you there.
巴衛君 いたの？
Just go.
（巴衛）出せ！
（瑞希）もう―
Sheesh, you're so violent, Tomoe.
乱暴なんだから 巴衛君は
奈々生がいなくなっただと
Nanami's... disappeared?
これだけ捜して
見つからないって―
If we can't find her after all the searching we've done...
Do you think she's left town?
奈々生ちゃん
もう街を出ちゃったのかな
白札を使ったか
So she has used a white talisman.
（きつね火１）
おい 見つかったか？
Hey, did you find her?
I haven't found her. I'm running on fumes here.
（きつね火５）
見つからないよ
俺 もうエンプティーだよ
Me too.
（きつね火１）
俺もだよ
Where in the world has Lady Nanami gotten to?
奈々生様 一体
どこへ行ってしまったのだろう
Air
（奈々生）
また 一人になっちゃった
I've ended up alone again.
Please
move
out
'
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Orders have been issued
to evict you and seize
your property.
Please
move
out
'
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
Off on a journey.
Don't look for me.
- Dad
What?!
I...
振り出しに戻っただけだ
I'm just back to square one!
I mean, me be a god?
私に神様だなんて…
振り出し…
Square one...
Someone!
（ミカゲ）
誰か 助けてください！
Please help me!
（ミカゲ）
その犬をどけてくださ～い！
Please get that dog out of here!
I will leave my home to you.
私の家を譲りますよ
You are more worthy of that house than I am.
私より あの家にふさわしい
今まで どこに行ってたんだ
Where have you been... all this time?
You call this a god?
こいつが土地神だと？
こんな小汚い娘に何ができる
What could a sorry-looking girl like her even do?
社など 別に潰れてもよい
I could not care less if this shrine goes to ruin.
Isn't the shrine your home?!
（奈々生）
あの社は
大事な あんたの家じゃない！
（女子生徒１）
今度の土日でしょう？
あそこの神社のお祭り
The festival at that shrine is this weekend, right?
何ていうんだっけ
What's it called again?
（女子生徒２）
“ミカゲ社”だって
It says Mikage Shrine here.
Let's invite Hide and Suzuki along too!
（女子生徒１）
ヒデ君と鈴木(すずき)君とかも誘おうよ
（女子生徒２）
いいね いいね
Totally! Good idea!
I so can't wait!
（女子生徒１）楽しみだよね
（女子生徒２）うん
Same here!
Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival!
October 21st 5pm~
We will be waiting
for you at the
Mikage Shrine!
Mikage Shrine
Autumn Festival!
October 21st 5pm~
We will be waiting
for you at the
Mikage Shrine!
あそこが… ミカゲ社が私の家だ
That place...
The shrine... is my home.
It's my home...
私の家は―
so I have to protect it!
私が守んなきゃ！
（きつね火１）
ハァー　奈々生様…
Lady Nanami.
Lady Nanami...
（きつね火２）奈々生様
（きつね火２のせきこみ）
（奈々生）うおーっ！
（きつね火たち）わっ！
（きつね火たち）
奈々生様 いた！
There she is!
I have to do it! I have to try!
やる やってみる！
I know I may not succeed.
できないかもしれない
できないかもしれないけど…
I know I may not succeed, but...
If there's anyone who can do it,
できるとしたら それは―
it has to be me!
私だけしか できないんだから～！
right up
Next part coming
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
What?
That is from the treasure storehouse.
（虎徹）
宝物庫から
Wh-What is this giant miasma?
（鬼切）
な… 何だ この巨大なしょう気は
（虎徹）
あっ！　しまった
Oh, no! I dropped the sacred sake!
神酒を落としてしまった
What is this?
（鬼切）
うん？　何だ これ
Even the miasma from earlier is being drawn into it!
今までのしょう気すら
吸い込まれてゆくぞ
Th-This is...
（虎徹）
こ… これは
What is happening?
（鬼切）
これは何だ 虎徹
Huh? What? What is going on?
（乙比古）
えっ 何… どうしたのこれ
This gigantic miasma...
こんなに巨大なしょう気
私の出したやつと違うわ
It's different from the one I released.
This wasn't supposed to happen!
想定外 想定外！
Return, miasma! Return to this small bottle!
お戻りなさい しょう気
この小瓶に お戻り！
What?
The miasma! Look at how big it's grown!
しょう気が…
あんなに大きくなってるよ
Master Tomoe.
（きつね火１）
巴衛様
We have found Lady Nanami.
（きつね火２）
奈々生様が見つかりました
Where is she?
（巴衛）
どこだ
Sir, she is currently headed for the Mikage Shrine.
（きつね火３）
はい
今 ミカゲ社に向かっております
What?
何…
（奈々生）
うりゃーっ！
Nanami!
奈々生！
Oh, th-the torii gate!
（虎徹）
ああ… と… 鳥居が
The shrine!
（鬼切）
社が…
There is no mistake. That is the miasma of the spider spirit.
（虎徹）
間違いない
これは土蜘蛛(つちぐも)のしょう気じゃ
Spider spirit?
（鬼切）
土蜘蛛の？
Do you not remember, Onikiri?
（虎徹）
覚えておらぬか 鬼切
It's the one Lord Mikage vanquished several hundred years ago!
数百年前に ミカゲ様が退治された
あの土蜘蛛じゃ
Oh, no!
Lord Mikage defeated the spirit, but its remaining miasma was far too tainted,
（虎徹）
あのとき
ミカゲ様は退治はしたが―
残った土蜘蛛のしょう気が
あまりにも汚れておったため―
so he was unable to completely
exorcise it and had to seal it away.
浄化しきれず
どこかに封印されたのじゃ
How was the seal broken?
（鬼切）
その封印が なぜに解かれたのじゃ
I do not know. I do not know, but...
（虎徹）
分からぬ… 分からぬが―
The one thing I do know is that there is nothing we can do about it!
我々に どうすることもできぬ
ことだけは分かる！
Kotetsu!
（鬼切）
虎徹！
（虎徹）ああ…
（鬼切）虎徹！
Kotetsu!
Max Tailwind!
（奈々生）
追い風ＭＡＸ！
Ah! Lady Nanami!
（鬼切･虎徹）おおっ 奈々生様！
（奈々生）やっ！
Hah!
Kotetsu.
（鬼切）虎徹
（虎徹）うう…
Lady Nanami!
（鬼切）
奈々生様
You have returned!
（虎徹）
戻られたのでございますね
Kotetsu, are you okay?!
虎徹君 大丈夫？
You must not, Lady Nanami.
（虎徹）
いけません 奈々生様
What?
（虎徹）
我らは―
We are supernatural beings, so we are fine,
あやかしの身でございますゆえ
大丈夫でございますが―
but it will be harmful for you to come into contact with it, so you must not!
奈々生様が お触れになっては
お体に障りますゆえ いけません
Kotetsu!
（鬼切）
虎徹…
Kotetsu...
虎徹君
I'm sorry! I'm sorry for disappearing without saying anything!
ごめんね
黙っていなくなったりして
Lady Nanami!
（鬼切）奈々生様！
（虎徹）奈々生様…
Lady Nanami!
Lady Nanami, it will be disastrous if this miasma reaches town.
（虎徹）
奈々生様 このしょう気が
街まで及んでしまったら―
大変なことになります
It... It must be stopped.
何とか…
何とか 食い止めませんと
Right. There are people looking
forward to the festival, after all.
お祭りを楽しみにしている
人たちがいるんだもん
I'll protect the town no matter what.
街は 絶対に守るよ
Lady Nanami!
（鬼切）奈々生様！
（虎徹）奈々生様！
（瑞希）
うわっ！　こ… これって…
Th-This is...
Where is Nanami?
奈々生は…
Nanami...
奈々生
A spider spirit?
（瑞希）
土蜘蛛？
I-It has begun to show its true form. It is definitely a spider spirit!
（鬼切）
しょ… 正体を現し始めました
土蜘蛛でございます
Shivvverrr...
I-It's way scary!
こ… 怖すぎる
Lady Nanami!
（鬼切）
奈々生様
Nanami!
奈々生
The spirit is backing away from her dance.
奈々生ちゃんの神楽で
土蜘蛛がひるんだ
There's no hesitation in her dance.
奈々生ちゃんの神楽
よどみがないよ
When did she get to be so...
いつの間に こんなに…
Lady Nanami is so beautiful!
（鬼切）
奈々生様 お美しい
And so brave!
（虎徹）
そして りりしい
Yes!
小娘…
Look at her...
Yes, she is lovely to watch.
（ミカゲ）
おお これは美しいですね
Mikage?
ミカゲ！
（奈々生）
右…
Right.
左…
Left.
前…
Front.
左…
Left.
（奈々生）右 左 右…
（巴衛）右 左 右…
Right.
Left.
That is right, Nanami. You remember well.
そうだ 奈々生 よく覚えている
Here it comes. The spot where you always stumble.
次だ　いつも つまずく箇所だ
（巴衛）あっ！
（瑞希）転んだ
She tripped.
Lady Nanami!
（鬼切･虎徹）
奈々生様！
Now?
ここで？
Oh, Lady Nanami!
（鬼切･虎徹）
ああっ 奈々生様！
キャーッ！
Tomoe!
巴衛
奈々生
Nanami!
You are the girl I have recognized as my lady and mistress.
お前は 俺が主人として認めた娘だ
臆することはない
You have nothing to fear.
巴衛！
Tomoe!
Nanami, your bells!
奈々生ちゃん 鈴！
瑞希
Mizuki!
I'll help you with your ritual dance too.
僕も奈々生ちゃんの神楽
応援するよ
Wheeeeeze
That girl...
あの娘…
She is exactly the girl that I believed her to be.
（ミカゲ）
やはり
私が思ったとおりの子でした
Mikage? Did you anticipate this from the very beginning?
ミカゲ あなた
初めから これ想定してたの？
Well...
（ミカゲ）
さあ…
Who knows?
どうでしょう
Th-This is...
こ… これ… ミカゲ
Mikage!
Mikage?
ミカゲ？
Nanami.
奈々生
Are you hurt at all?
けがは ないか
私 できたよ… できたよ 巴衛
I did it.
I did it, Tomoe.
Yes.
Lady Nanami.
（虎徹）奈々生様
（鬼切）虎徹も このとおり
And Kotetsu is also fine.
Oh, Kotetsu!
あっ 虎徹君
I'm so glad!
よかった… うん よかった
Yeah... I'm so glad!
Lady Nanami...
（虎徹）
奈々生様
Thank you very much!
（鬼切･虎徹）
ありがとうございました
Nanami, you truly are amazing.
奈々生ちゃん　ホントに すごいや
Tomoe.
（奈々生）巴衛
（巴衛）何だ
What is it?
（奈々生）受け止めて…
（巴衛）うん？
Catch me.
And then came the much-anticipated autumn festival.
（講釈師）
そして やって来ました
待望の秋祭り
Ooh, it looks to be a great success!
おお 大盛況じゃないですか
I've started the "being a girl" thing
The shrine's not abandoned at all, is it?
（主婦１）
全然 廃神社じゃないわよね
My sigh is like a violin playing
It's nice, isn't it? Good vibes everywhere!
（主婦２）
いいとこよね　パワスポ パワスポ
Wow, they really came!
わあ ホントに来てくれた
A red fruit has burst
I passed out quite a few fliers as well, after all.
俺も相当 ビラを配ったからな
I don't know you yet
But these festival arrangements... When did it get done?
（奈々生）
でも この祭りの設営 いつの間に？
（沼皇女(ぬまのひめみこ)）
我らが しつらえた
生きの良い若者たちを連れてきた
We made the preparations.
I brought some lively young folk with me.
（従女たち）
私たちが しつらえました
I say, "I've never done this before"
皇女(ひめみこ)！
Himemiko!
Your gaze is an evil flower,
どうしたの その服
すごく かわいい！
Where did you get that outfit? It's so cute!
blooming in riotous profusion
Truly?
誠か
Here is a bus stop leading to the forest, but you won't lead me
Hey, you freshwater fish!
Don't you dare start the party without me!
（龍王(りゅうおう)）
俺様抜きで
勝手に始めてんじゃねえぞ
Now that I, the great Dragon King, am here, I'll be the one anchoring this festival.
この龍王様が来たからには
祭りのトリは俺様のもんだ
When we link fingers we can feel the pulse of love
Wow, Dragon King, you came?!
わあ 龍王 来てくれたの
You, the land god, sent me a letter asking me to come, remember?!
The Mikage Shrine is doing an autumn festival. Please come.
土地神のお前(めえ)が“来てね”って
手紙くれたんだろうが
The Mikage Shrine is doing an autumn festival. Please come.
A soft magic
I had no choice but to come this far inland where it reeks of mammals.
しかたねえから―
哺乳類臭い陸にまで
上がってきてやったんだぜ
Lips that lie
Mammals?
哺乳類って
Yes, laid one upon the other
All of you so obviously look like spirits!
どっから見ても
一匹残らず妖怪ではないか
You know
At least try to hide your true identities!
少しは 正体を偽ってこい！
Please, dear God
What was that, you fox bastard?!
何だと きつね野郎
I want to be a bad girl
It reeks of mammals! Seriously!
哺乳類臭(くせ)えんだよな 哺乳類！
Lady Goddess of the Land.
（あやかし１）土地神様
（奈々生）はい？
Right now I'm being good,
Yes?
We are pleased to make your acquaintance.
（あやかし１）
お初に お目にかかります
so I'm begging you
We are the headsmen of the spirit kind who live in the land to the south.
我らは
南の地に住むあやかしのおさ
Let me be unfair for once,
We heard the land god would be performing a ritual dance, so we hastened here to attend.
土地神が神楽を舞われると聞き
はせ参じました
and when I want to be good anyway,
If we bear witness to your blessed dance...
（あやかし２）
土地神様の
ありがたい舞を拝めば…
blow up my skirt
...it shall spiritually invigorate us as well.
（あやかし３）
我らも精気が湧きまする
（一同）
ありがたや ありがたや
Truly a blessing to be thankful for.
and I'll go back
（女性）
見て あれ ＫＵＲＡＭＡ(クラマ)様よ！
Look! It's Kurama!
Looks like Saturday is going to be clear
やれやれ 今日は勘弁してくれよ
プライベートなんだからさ
Good grief. Give me a break today, will you?
This is personal time for me, after all.
Dear God, don't be mean to me
Hey, Nanami's back.
奈々生 帰ってんじゃねえか
If you dress that flashy, of course you'll be noticed.
プライベートで
あの派手な格好じゃバレるって
Hey, mask seller. Give me a mask.
（霧仁(きりひと)）
おい お面屋 面を１つくれ
Oh, in the hopes of finding love
Sure thing! This is called a death mask, and if you put it on, it...
はいは～い
これ 死に面っていってね
かぶると自分の…
I started putting up my hair and on its length
...shows your face in death, right?
（霧仁）
死に顔が浮かぶんだろう？
釣りは いらない
and on the apple tree, I swear
Keep the change.
I want to get to know you right now
He was human... right?
（瑞希）
人だよね？
Lady Nanami.
（鬼切･虎徹）
奈々生様
It is time for your ritual dance.
（虎徹）
神楽舞のお時間でございます
Oh, right.
We shall go prepare for you to get changed.
（鬼切）
お着替えの準備をしてまいります
We shall be waiting for you.
（虎徹）
お待ちしておりますゆえ
Okay. Uh...
ああ…
土蜘蛛相手には踊れたけど―
I was able to perform it in front of the spider spirit,
but the thought of dancing in front of a live
audience makes me nervous in a different way.
何か お祭りで―
The pirouette of butterflies flocking to a bouquet of flowers
お客さんの前で踊るのって
違う緊張だ　ハァー
You'll be fine, little girl.
（乙比古）大丈夫よ 小娘
（奈々生）えっ？
Hey, you're that he-she guy.
The dark torchlight
（奈々生）
あっ おばさんおじさんおばさん
Who are you calling he-she guy?
誰が おばさんおじさんおばさんよ
I ask with impudent lips
Here you go. I bought these snacks in town. You can have them.
はい これ
街で買ってきたお菓子 あげるわ
あ… ありが…
Oh, thank—
Knowing you, you can do it. Magnificently.
あんたならできるわよ 立派にね
"You know"
Please, dear God
So long, little girl.
Do you have no use for bad girls?
じゃあね 小娘
また どこかで会いましょ
Let's meet again somewhere.
I want to be a good girl
But it's rather late for that
After making me do this
（あみ）あっ！
（ケイ）おっ 奈々生
Look! It's Nanami!
Nanami.
奈々生
Oh-ho.
ほう
Wow...
（あみ）わあ…
（ケイ）おお
That night, the festival reached its zenith
（講釈師）
その夜 祭りは最高潮に達して―
and brilliantly lit up the hearts of all who attended.
訪れた者の心を
鮮やかに彩っていきました
I am glad that it was a great success.
（虎徹）
大盛況で ようございました
The rumors that the Mikage Shrine is abandoned will surely fade now.
（鬼切）
これで ミカゲ社が―
廃神社などという
うわさも消えましょう
You did great, Nanami.
（瑞希）
奈々生ちゃん お疲れさま
神楽きれいだったよ
Your dance was beautiful.
Thank you, Mizuki.
（奈々生）
ありがとう 瑞希
But my back is killing me... Owowow...
でも筋肉痛が… あ痛たた…
I hope we get more worshipers after this.
でも これで
参拝者が増えるといいね
Yeah!
Oh, we're all out of sake.
（瑞希）
あっ お酒なくなっちゃったね
I'll bring more.
お代わり持ってくるね
Oh, we shall go prepare something to go with it as well.
（虎徹）
ああ 我らも何か―
さかなになるものを
用意してまいりましょう
Onikiri.
（虎徹）鬼切
（鬼切）うん
Right.
So what did you think of my dance, Tomoe?
で… 巴衛はどうだった 私の神楽
Hm?
うん？　ああ 大したものだ
よくやった
Oh. It was quite an achievement. You did well.
Yeah. And?
うん それから？
And what? That is all.
それから？　それだけだ
That's all?
それだけ？
There's really nothing else?
もっと ないの？
瑞希みたいに きれいだったとか
I mean, Mizuki said it was beautiful.
Guess not, though.
ないんだ　フンッ
It was beautiful.
きれいだった
More beautiful than anything.
この世で いちばん
Huh? What was that? I couldn't hear you. Speak up!
えっ 何 何… 聞こえなかった
もう一度
What? Yes, you could!
何！　一度で聞け
Come on, one more time! One more time!
ねえ もう一度 もう一度！
Oh, shut up!
（巴衛）
黙れ
Okay, I heard you loud and clear.
ちゃんと聞こえたよ うれしい
I'm happy.
Nanami.
（巴衛）
奈々生
May I seal the contract of the familiar with you?
神使の契約をしてもよいか
What? But the familiar contract...
えっ 神使の契約なら…
It is from the heart.
心からだ
ah ah ah ah
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
Goodbye
ah ah ah